{
    "id": "ff75444da9a84153b456125279e508b6",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Put",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She puts ...................... a small amount every month towards her retirement.",
            "description": "To put something by is to save an amount of money to use later. ",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "by",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2ea75198b16d4e16b64a54f7bffca6ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "The meeting has been put ...................... until Thursday.",
            "description": "To put off is to postpone. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "90fbfe4bc9e348709e97bd66d1a153f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is just putting ...................... an act to win your sympathy.",
            "description": "To put on an act is to fake and pretend. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7869521e04cd467aa806fbe836a6dff6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I cannot put ............................... this heat.",
            "description": "To put up with something is to tolerate it. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "up with",
                "out with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "426a62eb12fe4be595d423096308c115"
        },
        {
            "question": "The firemen worked hard to put .......................... the fire.",
            "description": "To put out fire is to extinguish it. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5472a46b16be45f3a43a6d012f48f11d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Could you put me ............................. to the manager?",
            "description": "To put x through to y is to connect x and y. ",
            "answers": [
                "through",
                "into",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ee1e54d9e208400180e664baa56354af"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don't forget to put the lights ........................ when you leave.",
            "description": "To put lights out is to switch them off. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "off",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "425bad78db724b8d81344dba58f2559c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am sorry to have to put you ....................... this.",
            "description": "To put somebody through something is to cause them to experience something. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "through",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "166ad1e4eabc4a8aa4f782605b5a443f"
        },
        {
            "question": "You need good communication skills to be able to put your message ......................",
            "description": "To put your message across is to communicate it. ",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "across",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cc44a398d5b443cf86c6d8c7915affa8"
        },
        {
            "question": "My professor has agreed to put a good word .................... for me.",
            "description": "To put a word in for somebody is to recommend them. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "153c34be8e18464ab5b0e297f4be7c98"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better put your coat ....................... before going out. It is very cold outside.",
            "description": "To put on clothes is to wear them. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "over",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f0bf26ada0f341f9bcaf35483dcfcbdd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Everybody liked the suggestion put ........................... by Susie.",
            "description": "To put forward a suggestion is to present it for other people's consideration. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "through",
                "forward"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bbd115d973f042c089df2e78a35f832f"
        }
    ]
}